jobgurusng.com 2014-11-11

# 

**Overview**  
jobgurus.com.ng (“jobgurus.com.ng”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This policy describes the types of information collected, how it may and may not be used, and how it is protected. By visiting jobgurus.com.ng’s website ("Website"), or using any of our services on the website ("Website Services"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and our use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on jobgurus.com.ng to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**Third Party Sites**  
jobgurus.com.ng does not control the privacy policies of third party sites or service providers to which we provide links. These third party sites or service providers may use cookies to provide a service or serve ads based on a user's prior visits to jobgurus.com.ng. Please be aware that if you click on an ad or third party link, you will be subject to the third party's privacy policy.

**Changes to the jobgurus.com.ng Privacy Policy**  
You agree that jobgurus.com.ng may amend this policy from time to time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Your continued use of any portion of the Website or jobgurus.com.ng service following the posting of the revised policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**Information Collected From Users**  
In the course of your browsing the Website, jobgurus.com.ng may collect the IP address of the computer through which your visit is enabled; cookie information; information regarding the pages, links, banners, icons and other parts of the Website that are accessed or clicked on during a visit to the Website; information regarding the date, time, and duration of your visit; and information you may volunteer, e.g., in response to survey requests or as part of a registration. Upon any registration for, and in subsequent interaction with, Website Services, jobgurus.com.ng may collect mandatory information such as your User Name, Password, primary email address, etc. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer when you visit a website. jobgurus.com.ng uses a cookie for record-keeping and verification purposes and a cookie helps us provide better service to you. For example, we use a cookie to verify your session and user identification and to track the pages within the Website that you visited. Your browser should have options to accept, reject or provide you with a notice when a cookie is sent. However, if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use the Website Services. Please note that jobgurus.com.ng does not and cannot read cookies set by other websites. 

**Your obligations to other Users**  
As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members. Do not abuse the jobgurus.com.ng service by using it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate this Privacy Policy. You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of jobgurus.com.ng and its community of Users. 

**Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk. We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf.

**Use of Information Collected**  
We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customized user experience. We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. Your information will not be shared with any third parties except as explained below.

As part of our business, we may pass to our service partners aggregated information (data gathered up across multiple or all user accounts) regarding visitors, users, and historical transactions in a manner that will not personally identify any individual user. We may aggregate personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

We will not sell, rent or transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party, unless we are required by law, court order or regulation, or we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with law or legal process, or to cooperate with local or federal authorities, or to protect or defend against fraud, misuse of the jobgurus.com.ng Website, breach of any of your obligations hereunder, or to protect our intellectual property rights. In addition, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of the assets of jobgurus.com.ng to another company (an "Acquirer Company"), provided that such Personally Identifiable Information shall only be used by the Acquirer Company in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. jobgurus.com.ng will not track your Internet usage outside of the confines of the jobgurus.com.ng Website. 

**How to contact us**  
You can contact jobgurus.com.ng by sending an email to [info@jobgurus.com.ng](mailto:info@jobgurus.com.ng)
